I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know
I don't know, I don't know
I don't know
I'm alone, goodbye, goodbye
I'm alone, I'm alone, goodbye
I'm alone, goodbye
Chantum ritsham ah yang kachi kejipro puntae mongtum mongtutru
Sum shwam beh dungui ni pongta bante
Yung min ni saiban krabk bahe knung nien jiswam bai bantrat nung tuai grubbe
Aklung dung te kan song tan pik min kai ning pa kan song ah ya rom kong hang prai zeng
Mung hon keng chung a khyong chung mung klun aik
Bleig ho srohan keng sonik
Pong pra trang nang sroy
Tai nel lo lo bambai
Dung hui ni pong ta bante
Misai bang krap kpang
Jiswa may bant nang